<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="146044" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Hover Colors" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
    <ShortDescription Value="Change blue outlines to Any color or transparency. Surface layers on/off, District colors."/>
    <!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<LongDescription>
## Mochi's Hover Colors

### Reduce blue
- **1-Click disable**/enable all blue outlines on the fly - in the city UI.
- or change highlight transparency (alpha) and color.
- Full highlight control: buildings, cars, trees, citizens, more!

#### Things to make life easier
- **Guidelines** change color+ opacity so you see more than just white line with blue!
- **Surfaces** turn off preview layers while using the Surface tool so you can see the real ground colors without cloudy layers on top. Hotkeys for easy workflow.
- **Specialized Industry** button does the same for farms/excavators.
- **District tool** change the color + opacity of district borders and overlays, or turn them off completely.
- These extras don't cost more to have per performance; can reset the extra colors to game default if you like.

## Important
- Lightweight - no Harmony patches - all vanilla; means safer, more compatible with other mods and the game, designed for optimal gameplay.
- Bulldozer and Road-tool color behavior: check Options menu!
- Turn off mod tooltips - click the Info button, top-left, in-city panel.
- Darker panel option. Good for LegacyUI or players who prefer darker contrast. Try both standard and dark to see what you like!
- Alpha = transparency; use the last bar on the color picker.
-   Tap preset 1 or 2 to switch your saved colors.
-   Change presets: select a color swatch box 1/row1, then hold preset 1 or 2 until the fill bar sweeps across - done. Reset button flips between your saved color or mod default.
- Read the tooltips or Options Menu 3rd panel if you get lost.
- Save-game safe and safe to remove any time.
- Works with *Recolor* - HC does highlights, guidelines, overlays; not object color like yen's Recolor mod. Even HC's Color Picker is a vanilla component.
- Performance Optimized: when the panel is closed, it is not doing active layout work; the C# systems mostly sit idle, example, you change a color, mod takes action, then goes back idle.

### Feedback
- Please send suggestions, bug reports, or just say hi!
- This took many months to overcome many obstacles in game code.
- Please share and Like ! -- River Mochi

## ❤️ Special Thanks
- **Huge shout out to everyone who tested or supported the mod on its 7 month journey to release.**
- Flashbond - collab, tech feedback, testing
- yenyang - collab, tech feedback, testing
- StarQ - tech feedback, testing
- gagaxm - feature idea, testing
- Dx, Necko1996, BugsyG, ElGendo87, Maestro - testing
- =Noel= Thumbnail, testing
- rzzirrah - images1 consultant

### 12+ Languages
- English, Français, Deutsch, Español, Italiano, Polski, 简体中文 , 한국어
- Português Brasil, 繁體中文 , 日本語, Thai ภาษาไทย, Tiếng Việt, Turkish Türkçe, EU Portuguese Português

tags: Mochi's blue scrubber, Highlight, border color, remove blue, guidelines, district colors, surface tool, custom colors, transparency.

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail_half_building_cyan.jpg" />
    <!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/01-image-ReleaseTheBlueAlpha.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/05-image-Before-after-DE-school.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/15-image-ColorPicker.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/20-image-Options.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/30-image-Guidelines.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/35-image-AreaLots.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/40-image-DistrictColorPicker.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/55-image-Fence.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/mochis-hover-colors.1925898/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<ChangeLog>
- Resize main color outline swatch, add styling and dot indicator
- Added Collapsible panel arrow
- Mod Tooltips now can only be turned off from Options menu to prevent player accidental turn off
- info icon can only turn on tooltip but not off.
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
    <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/CS2-Mochi-HoverColors" />
    <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/gwXgvtyhjc" />

	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
